<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Sweet Nothings!]]></title>
  <link href="http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/"/>
  <updated>2015-08-27T15:10:25-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Latoya Robinson]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[mzlppope@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Nine]]></title>
    <link href="http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/19/blog-nine/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-19T15:40:02-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/19/blog-nine</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>+# YWeb, Colhart 2, Week 1
+</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Eight]]></title>
    <link href="http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/07/blog-eight/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-07T12:18:49-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/07/blog-eight</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>WEEK 8!</p>

<p>Week 8 has definitely been the busiest week for me. I have so much work to do, and honestly half of it is late work but its getting done and im almost where I need to be. I'v been working on CSS, JQuery, Javascript, my portfolio, and some networking fundamentals. It&rsquo;s a lot of work but it has to be done. I&rsquo;m excited to learn more and can&rsquo;t wait to start the up and comming projects.</p>

<p>Who ever was responsible for the trip to Zendesk I want to thank you so much for that opportunity. Everything about the people and the place was just amazing. Even if I never see that place again, I will never forget that experience or the staff.</p>

<p>A special thanks to Jillian, me and my classmates thought she did a wonderful job.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Seven]]></title>
    <link href="http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/31/blog-seven/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-31T12:14:30-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/31/blog-seven</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Week 7 Blog! This week has definitely been a challenge for me. There&rsquo;s a lot of things thats due , and a lot to be done. I&rsquo;m currently working on code school, my portfolio-css skeleton, java-script and at the same time thinking about what i&rsquo;m going to blog about. I feel like i&rsquo;m all over the place doing so much but i&rsquo;m barley completing anything. I wish I could find a place with more space in my head so that when i&rsquo;m thinking it&rsquo;s clear. So not only will I be able to complete my work but get organized and turn my assignments in on time. My report card is not ok, although it&rsquo;s a reflection of me, I soon will be where I need to be in order to complete this program.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Six]]></title>
    <link href="http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/24/blog-six/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-24T12:08:52-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/24/blog-six</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Week 6 has been a very busy week, we was givin a lot of work but it was expected. I focused more on HTML, CSS and code school more then JavsScript this week. I need to get more intune with JavaScript because its more of a challenge for me, so if anyone have any ideas of how i can get a better understanding about it inform me please and thank you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Five]]></title>
    <link href="http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/17/blog-five/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-17T12:00:43-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/17/blog-five</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We in week five and thanks to my new family(the class) we all made it through. I really enjoyed week five, not as hard as week four but thats ok.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Four]]></title>
    <link href="http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/10/blog-four/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-10T11:49:05-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/10/blog-four</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>week four is finally over. time is starting to go by really fast. thanks to both the awesome teachers and the helpful class mates im getting through this.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Three]]></title>
    <link href="http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/03/blog-three/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-03T11:38:02-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/03/blog-three</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Week three was very har for me but, im going to keep going over chapter 2 worksheet until i git it. I&rsquo;m thankful for everyones help and I know i will get it soon.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Two]]></title>
    <link href="http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/26/blog-two/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-26T11:29:04-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/26/blog-two</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Week two in the yweb program. Alot of infomation a lot to remember a lot to learn. Java script is very interesting, but I like it.ß</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog One]]></title>
    <link href="http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/19/blog-one/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-19T12:29:21-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://latoyahr1.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/19/blog-one</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>+# YWeb, Colhart 2, Week 1
+
+Week 1 is finally done&hellip;.Yaaaah!
+
+I&rsquo;ve learned a lot this week, and really looking forward to learning more.
+</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
